策划了一场无效审判
By engineering a mistrial.
开玩笑吧
Seriously?
我很抱歉  什么
I'm sorry, what?
我说「开玩笑吧」
I said, "Seriously?"
这也太简单了吧
It just seems pretty convenient,
福瑞克就这么应承了你要他做的事
Florrick admitting exactly what you need him to.
加伯先生所说的证词
Mr. Garber is giving
可是宣过誓的
sworn testimony.
宣誓是宣誓了
That he practiced.
但还得看他是否把其他事也记得如此清楚
But see if he remembers anything else that clearly.
上周二的午饭你吃了什么
What did you have for lunch last Tuesday?
你不必回答这个问题  加伯先生
Uh, you-you don't have to answer that, Mr. Garber.
你说过我们想问什么都行
You said we could ask anything we want.
没错  任何相关的问题  先生
Yes. Anything relevant, sir.
为何这个问题就不相关
Why isn't this relevant?
我们全都在听你的提问
We've been listening to all your questioning.